[UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC]
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
♪ HEY LADIES ♪
♪ HEY MA. WHAT'S UP ♪
♪ LET'S SLIDE, ALL
RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU SMOKE, I SMOKE ♪
- WHAT'S GOING ON LADIES.
♪ I DRINK, ME TOO, WELL GOOD ♪
HOW YOU DOING?
PARDON ME SIR.
♪ CAUSE WE GONNA GET TONIGHT ♪
♪ GOT DROPS, GOT COUPES ♪
♪ GOT TRUCKS ♪
DOG YOU NOT OLD ENOUGH
TO GET IN YOU 18.
♪ GOT JEEPS ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT ♪
- WHAT'S REALLY
GOOD WITH YOU FAM?
♪ CAUSE WE GONNA
TAKE A RIDE TONIGHT ♪
- YOU GOTTA BE 21 TO GET IN.
♪ SO MA, WHAT'S UP ♪
- YOU NOT GONNA
LET ME IN THE CLUB?
♪ LET'S SLIDE, ALL RIGHT ♪
- CAN'T LET YOU GO IN
♪ ALL RIGHT ♪
YOU CAN'T EVEN
DRINK MY LIQUOR. YO, YO, YO.
♪ AND WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ NOW I WAS DOWNTOWN
CLUBBIN', LADIES NIGHT ♪
♪ SEEN SHORTY SHE
WAS CRAZY RIGHT ♪
♪ AND I APPROACH BABY LIKE ♪
♪ MA, WHAT'S YOUR AGE AND TYPE ♪
♪ SHE LOOKED AT ME AND
SAID USE A BABY RIGHT ♪
♪ I TOLD HER, I'M 18
AND LIVE A CRAZY LIFE ♪
♪ PLUS I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT THE 80'S LIKE ♪
♪ AND I KNOW WHAT LADIES LIKE ♪
♪ NEED A MAN THAT'S POLITE,
LISTENS AND TAKES ADVICE ♪
♪ I COULD BE ALL THREE,
PLUS I CAN LAY THE PIPE ♪
♪ COME WITH ME COME
STAY THE NIGHT ♪
♪ SHE LOOKED AT ME LAUGHIN',
LIKE BOY YOUR GAME IS TIGHT ♪
♪ I'M LAUGHIN' BACK
LIKE SHOW YOU RIGHT ♪
♪ GET IN THE CAR ♪
♪ AND DON'T TOUCH
NOTHING SIT IN THE CAR ♪
♪ LET DISCUSS SOMETHIN' ♪
♪ EITHER WE LOVIN' OR
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW ♪
♪ NOW WE SPEEDING
UP THE WESTSIDE ♪
♪ HAND CREEPIN' UP HER LEFT
SIDE, I'M READY TO DO IT ♪
♪ READY TO BONE,
READY FOR DOME ♪
♪ 55TH EXIT, DAMN,
DAMN, ALREADY WE HOME ♪
♪ NOW LET'S GET IT ON ♪
♪ HEY MA, WHAT'S UP, LETS
SLIDE, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU SMOKE, I SMOKE, I
DRINK, ME TOO, WELL GOOD ♪
♪ CAUSE WE GONNA GET TONIGHT ♪
♪ GOT DROPS, GOT COUPES, GOT
TRUCKS, GOT JEEPS, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA TAKE
A RIDE TONIGHT ♪
♪ SO MA, WHAT'S UP, LET'S
SLIDE, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ HOLLA HOLLA ♪
♪ R-O-C ♪
♪ UH ♪
[INDISTINCT]
♪ WE GON SET THIS OFF. ♪
♪ MY IS A KILLER ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ BUT WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ NOW THAT I GOT A GIRL, MY
EX WANNA HOLLA AND SPIT ♪
♪ TOLD ME TO
ACKNOWLEDGE HER QUICK ♪
♪ SHE LIKE CAM STOP FRONTIN' ♪
♪ ON THAT DAVE HOLLISTER TIP ♪
♪ COME OVER LETS
SWALLOW AND SIP ♪
♪ I'M LIKE MOMMA THAT'S IT ♪
♪ I PROMISE YOU DICK, USUALLY
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH CHICKS ♪
♪ THEY ALL SAY I'M
ROTTEN AND RICH ♪
♪ BUT NOT HER, BOOBY'S REAL ♪
♪ HIGH HEEL DOOBY FEEL, PLUS
GOT THEM GUCCI NAILS, UH ♪
♪ YOU A CUTIE STILL, AND
THIS MY DOWN GIRL TOO ♪
♪ AIN'T NO GROUPIE DEAL ♪
♪ WE LEFT THE MOVIES WITH
UZIES, SUZUKI WHEELS, ♪
♪ TO THE JACUZZI, I TELL
YOU MY BOOBY'S REAL ♪
♪ I MEAN SHE DO BE
WINNING, LUEY SPINNING ♪
♪ GO TO THE CRIB SHE
GOT THE GUCCI LINEN' ♪
♪ I SEE BOO BE GRINNING ♪
♪ SHE LOOKED AND SAID CAM,
I KNOW THAT YOU BE SINNING ♪
♪ NO, I'M A CHANGED MAN,
LOOK AT THE RANGE MAIM ♪
♪ I GOT A WHOLE NEW GAME PLAN ♪
♪ LOOKED AND SAID THAT'S
NOTHING BUT GAME CAM ♪
♪ SHE WAS RIGHT, SHE WAS
UP IN THE RANGE MAN ♪
♪ DROPPED HER OFF AT THE L,
NOW I'M FLIPPIN' THE CELL ♪
♪ THAT'S RIGHT I
HAD TO CALL UP L ♪
♪ YO L, WHAT UP, I HIT, WHAT
ELSE, PLUS DOME, SAY WORD ♪
♪ AND WE GOT IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ HEY MA, WHAT'S UP, LET'S
SLIDE, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU SMOKE, I SMOKE, I
DRINK, ME TOO, WELL GOOD ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE GONNA GET TONIGHT ♪
♪ GOT DROPS, GOT COUPES, GOT
TRUCKS, GOT JEEPS, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA TAKE
A RIDE TONIGHT ♪
♪ SO MA, WHAT'S UP, LET'S
SLIDE, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ AND WE GONNA GET
IT ON TONIGHT ♪
[UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC]
♪♪♪